{
    "interview": [     
        {
            "question": "What does HTML mean?",
            "choices": ["Hyper Text Markup Language", "Hidden Text Markup Langauge", "Hyper Text Manage Language", "How To Make Lasagna"],
            "correct": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "What type of tag is '< br/>'?",
            "choices": ["break tag", "broken tag", "body tag", "bad tag"],
            "correct": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is an example of an empty element?",
            "choices": ["< /img>", "< img></img>", "< img>", "< img>empty</img>"],
            "correct": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "How does an HTML document start?",
            "choices": ["< DOCTYPE! html>", "< HTML doctype!>", "< HTML! doctype>", "< !DOCTYPE html>"],
            "correct": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you size your HTML to fit any size viewport?",
            "choices": ["With a < script> tag", "With a media query", "With firebase", "It automatically sizes"],
            "correct": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "What symbol is associated with class?",
            "choices": ["#", "$", ".", "%"],
            "correct": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many HTML headings are there?",
            "choices": ["5", "7", "6", "8"],
            "correct": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you add a script tag?",
            "choices": ["add < script", "< script>", "< scriptto>", "< scripts>"],
            "correct": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "What's the name of the new HTML5 element that begins with the letter K?",
            "choices": ["keys", "kit", "kygo", "keygen"],
            "correct": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "What file extension should hml files have",
            "choices": ["html", "web", "page", "site"],
            "correct": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is making the Web standards?",
            "choices": ["Google", "World Internt Committee", "World Wide Web Consortium", "International Web Authority (IWA)"],
            "correct": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which tag is used to create paragraphs?",
            "choices": ["< par>", "< p>", "< pg>", "< p."],
            "correct": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "To create a link to an anchor, which property in <a> tag is used?",
            "choices": ["src", "link", "name", "href"],
            "correct": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Choose the correct HTML tag for the most important heading",
            "choices": ["h6", "head", "h1", "title"],
            "correct": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "How can you make a list that lists the items with numbers?",
            "choices": ["< ul>", "< li>", "< wn>", "< ol>"],
            "correct": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where do you link to your css file?",
            "choices": ["in the < body>", "in the ,< head>", "before the < head> ", "after the < body>"],
            "correct": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Choose the correct HTML tag for the most important heading",
            "choices": ["h6", "head", "h1", "title"],
            "correct": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "What HTML version is in current use?",
            "choices": ["HTML5", "HTML4", "HTML7", "HTML3"],
            "correct": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is correct?",
            "choices": ["< b/>hi< b>", "< b = hi/>", "hi< b>", "< b>hi< /b>"],
            "correct": "4"
        }
    ]
}
